addicted-2-retail.com 2010-11-25

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to Adddicted-2-Retail.com is important to us.

Like manny websites on the internet we use third party advertisements on Adddicted-2-Retail.com to help support our site. Bandwith is expensive. If you would like to prevent all third party advertisements from being displayed simply register for free. 

You can join absolutely free and even submit your own blog posts for consideration on the site. As long as you are logged in you will not see ads displayed on our site. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We will never sell your email address or personal information to third parties. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Adddicted-2-Retail.com, and how we safeguard your information. 

Some of our third party advertisers such as Google may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Google DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

Infolinks Contextual Advertisements  
We also display contextual Advertisements through infolinks. Please be aware of Infolinks Pricay Policy as well at [ http://www.infolinks.com/privacy.html;jsessionid=84001A9FABCDFCD0044F336075768964](http://www.infolinks.com/privacy.html;jsessionid=84001A9FABCDFCD0044F336075768964)

Just like any other website on the internet our websites computer severs collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Verizon or Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or [Firefox](http://www.mozilla.com/en-US/firefox/firefox.html)), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

Your browser is immpotant. It is desinded to send and recieve infomation about you and the websites you vist. It also controls how your computer can handle and deliver the offen interactive aspects of a website. That is why we would like to invite anyone who is still using internet explore to upgrade to a better browser and ereance the web in hd. Here are two of my personal faviorate web browsers.
